adxpansion.com 2010-10-08

# AdXpansion - Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

### Information Collected and How It's Used

#### Information you provide

When you sign up for a service that requires registration, we ask you for personal information (such as your name, email address and an account password). For certain services, we also request credit card or other payment account information which we maintain in encrypted form on secure servers. We may combine the information you submit under your account with information from other AdXpansion services or third parties in order to provide you with a better experience and to improve the quality of our services.

#### Cookies

When you visit this website, we send one or more cookies to your computer, which is a small file containing a string of characters. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service, including for storing user preferences, improving ad selection, and tracking user trends. AdXpansion also uses cookies in its services to help advertisers and publishers serve and manage ads across the web. We may set one or more cookies in your browser when you visit our websites, including sites that use our advertising cookies, and view or click on an ad supported by AdXpansion's advertising services. 

#### Log information

When you access AdXpansion services, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. 

#### User communications

When you send email or other communications to AdXpansion, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services. 

#### Affiliated Services on other sites

We offer some of our services on or through other web sites. Personal information that you provide to those sites may be sent to AdXpansion in order to deliver the service. We process such information under this Privacy Policy. The affiliated sites through which our services are offered may have different privacy practices and we encourage you to read their privacy policies. 

### Disclosure of Your Information

AdXpansion does not rent or sell any personal information provided by you or about you to any third party without your permission. We may share with third parties certain pieces of aggregated, non-personal information, such as how many users clicked on a particular advertisement. Such information does not identify you individually. Certain information, such as your password, credit card number, and bank information, will not be disclosed in aggregate at all. We provide such information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies or other trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of processing personal information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. 

### Information security

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data.

We restrict access to personal information to our employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations. 

### Accessing and updating personal information

When you use AdXpansion services, we make good faith efforts to provide you with access to your personal information and either to correct this data if it is inaccurate or to delete such data at your request if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes. We ask individual users to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical, or for which access is not otherwise required. In any case where we provide information access and correction, we perform this service free of charge, except if doing so would require a disproportionate effort. 

### Changes to This Privacy Policy

We may change this policy as new services are added or old ones are changed. We will post any Privacy Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice. Please check this Privacy Policy from time to time for updates by checking the date of the "Last Update" at the top of this document. 

If you have any additional questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us any time through this web site Contact Us page.
